Hello.
Next, we're going to set up, so I'll play a character.
We'll play that dashing animation.
When that dashing if we head over to the animations folder and go to the warrior animation source.
Due to add new and new animation sequence.
I'm just going to rename this to be dashing.
And then we'll go through animation data and set what?
Next if we open up our animation blueprint.
And make sure we're in the new state machine with people's ID.
They invented this clever new feature called Jump nodes.
Jump nodes basically allow it so we can force our animation blueprint to start specific animation no
matter where we are.
In order to implement a jump node, just right click and select jump.
Just rename this and call this dash.
Ben Dreykov here and for animation state and just call this dashing.
Double click and head inside here.
And then right click on it for play.
That's.
And just hook this up here.
And from dashing connect and hook this to Idol run and to jumping.
So if we're in our state and we want to enter our state, we're just going to double click inside here
and right click and for time remaining.
Four time remaining dashing.
I'm going to check to see that the time remaining of our animation is less than.
0.1.
And so it's a struggle him and and if our blueprint reference.
If they're currently in working mode.
So look for is walking.
Because up to here.
Then enter our transition.
So if my play character enters that dashing transition and then there's no point 1 seconds left of the
animation and my character is walking, then we'll make them enter their walk and stay.
If my character is doing that dashing animation and the time remaining when the animation.
Is.
Is less than 0.1.
And if my character is fool, so will this time drag?
And I'll play BP.
And for.
Is falling.
Then we'll enter our falling animation state.
So I'm just going to drag this to the top.
I think that's a better position.
I mean, it's a bit more clear.
Then we can compile and save.
So inside of our player, BP, we're going to force our animation to enter the state whenever our player
character is dashing, and that will just force it to play the data, the animation.
So we go back to our player, BP.
After this two months, we can drag in this animation component.
Then you want to drag off here and get an instance.
Ben track four jump to Node and I got from that.
Who wants to hear?
And I got from here to here.
It's going to ask us the jump name.
So I called my dash.
So you want to get what have you called yours and make sure that you spelt it correctly and type it
in here.
So now when we press the dashboard inside of our animation component, it's going to force us to enter
this dash data and then we'll enter our dash and animation.
Then once it's over, depending whether we're walking or depending whether we're falling, it will enter
the relevant correct animation.
So now I can just close this.
Go play.
And my desk when I'm on the ground, I do my Dutch examination.
If I check up on the Dutch, I do.
My doesn't count.
And then I do my morning animation.
So with that, we have set up getting animation and also the editing system.